A Guide to the Taconic Foundation records FA407
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1958-2010; 1; 76.73 Cubic Feet 172 document boxes (including 1 half-box), 2 oversized flat boxes; 2.02 Gigabytes 35 digital files
  - Fifth Avenue Committee: LEAP, Inc.
    - 1996 (Box 48, Folder 494)
    - 1997-1999 (Box 48, Folder 495)
  - First Church of Christ (Congregational) in Northampton, MA. See Northern Educational Service.
  - First Lady's Committee for a More Beautiful Capital, 1967, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 496)
  - Fish, Hamilton, Jr., 1983-1990 (Box 48, Folder 497)
    Press releases and correspondence concerning youth employment and child care initiatives, Women's Leadership programs, voter registration, etc. File includes one color snapshot photograph of Fish speaking at an event.
  - Fisk University (Congregational Christian Churches), 1958, 1960-1961 (Box 48, Folder 498)
    Support for study of employment practices of federal government contractors in southern states. Grant awarded to the Race Relations Department of the Congregational Christian Churches, at Fisk University.
  - Flowers with Care, 1982-1984 (Box 48, Folder 499)
    Job and counseling program for at-risk youth.
  - Flowers with Care, 1985, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 500)
    - Group Thanksgiving meal, 1990; 2014:FA407:029; 3 still images (Item 2014:FA407:029)
  - Forest Neighborhood House: General, 1966-1967; 1969-1970 (Box 48, Folder 501)
    In 1969 the organization's name changed to the Forest-Gould Neighborhood Center.
  - Forest Neighborhood House: Advocacy Project, 1966-1970 (Box 48, Folder 502)
  - Fort Greene - Navy Yard Area Youth Program, Inc., 1965-1966 (Box 49, Folder 503)
  - Forum Institute, 1982-1983 (Box 49, Folder 504)
    Grant to strengthen legal services for the poor. For earlier grants see American Bar Association, Legal Services Back-Up Centers.
  - Foundation Center
    - 1972-1978 (Box 49, Folder 505)
    - 1979-1984 (Box 49, Folder 506)
    - 1985-1988 (Box 49, Folder 507)
    - 1989-1991 (Box 49, Folder 508)
    - 1992-1994 May (Box 48, Folder 509)
    - 1994 June - 1996 (Box 49, Folder 510)
    - 1997-2004 (Box 49, Folder 511)
    - 2005-2007 (Box 50, Folder 512)
  - Foundation for Children and the Classics, 1996-1997 (Box 50, Folder 513)
  - Foundation for Children and the Classics, 1998-2002 (Box 50, Folder 514)
  - Foundation for Cooperative Housing, 1966, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 515)
  - Foundation for Cooperative Housing, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 516)
  - Fresh Youth Initiatives, 1999-2001 (Box 50, Folder 517)
    Support for Center for Community Service Education.
  - Anna Freud Foundation: General
    - 1960-1963 (Box 50, Folder 518)
    - 1964-1968, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 519)
  - Anna Freud Foundation: Reports
    Files contain papers, research and statistical reports, and case studies from the Hampstead Child-Therapy Clinic, in London.
    - 1963-1965, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 520)
    - 1964-1967 (Box 50, Folder 521)
    - 1964-1967 (Box 51, Folder 522)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 51, Folder 523)
    - circa 1966, undated (Box 51, Folder 524)
  - Friends of Island Academy, 1999-2006 (Box 51, Folder 525)
    Rikers Island, New York.
  - Friends of the Children New York, 2001-2005 (Box 51, Folder 526)
  - Fund for an OPEN Society
    Support to develop a leasing-cooperative housing program to benefit low- and moderate-income families in Philadelphia.
    - 1982 - 1983 March (Box 51, Folder 527)
    - 1983 April - 1987 (Box 51, Folder 528)
  - Futures and Options Inc., 2000-2005 (Box 51, Folder 529)
  - Gamaliel Foundation
    Support toward the costs of litigation brought by the Contract Buyers League on behalf of African American homebuyers in Chicago, who faced discriminatory practices in real estate pricing and financing.
    - 1969 (Box 51, Folder 530)
    - 1970-1973 (Box 52, Folder 531)
    - 1974, 1977-1978 (Box 52, Folder 532)
  - Ganzglass, Evelyn, 1982, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 532 A)
    File contains a small amount of correspondence with Jane Lee Eddy concerning Smokey House, the New York City Youth Energy Corps, and youth employment.
  - Georgia Council on Human Relations
    - 1970, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 533)
      - Emergency School Assistance Project, circa 1972 March; 2014:FA407:030; 2 still images (Item 2014:FA407:030)
        Two images of children in integrated classroom, Savannah, GA. Enclosed in James L. Draper to Jane Lee Eddy, 1972 March 21.
    - 1973 (Box 52, Folder 534)
    - 1974 (Box 52, Folder 535)
  - Gibson, James O., 1971-1972, 1983, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 536)
  - Girls, Inc.
    - 1995-2001 (Box 52, Folder 537)
    - 2002 (Box 52, Folder 538)
    - 2003 (Box 52, Folder 539)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 540)
  - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: General
    Support for a remedial tutoring program and for Operation Friend, a program to improve community and police relations.
    - 1963-1967 (Box 53, Folder 541)
    - 1968-1974 (Box 53, Folder 542)
    - 1978-1980 (Box 53, Folder 543)
  - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Operation Friend, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 544)
    Operation Friend, a program to improve relations between police and Puerto Rican communities in New York, sponsored a cultural exchange trip to Puerto Rico for a group of New York City patrolmen and a visit to New York for Puerto Rican children.
    - Operation Friend trips, 1965; 2014:FA407:031; 11 still images (Item 2014:FA407:031)
  - Gold, Neil N., and Paul Davidoff. See Davidoff and Gold Project (Lower Manhattan Low Income Housing Study).
  - Goldmark, Peter C., Jr., 1982-1984, 1988-1991 (Box 53, Folder 545)
    As director of the Port Authority, Peter Goldmark established a pilot program to hire Youth Energy Corps trainees as Port Authority employees.
  - Good Hope Baptist Church. See Second Good Hope Baptist Church.
  - Good Old Lower East Side, Inc., 1992-1994 (Box 53, Folder 546)
  - Good Old Lower East Side, Inc., 1995-1997 (Box 53, Folder 547)
  - Good Shepherd Services, 2006-2007 (Box 53, Folder 548)
  - Goodwyn, Lawrence, 1970-1971 (Box 53, Folder 549)
  - Graduate School of Political Management, 1992, 1994-1995 (Box 53, Folder 550)
    Taconic Foundation officer Jane Lee Eddy was on the board of the Graduate School of Political Management. Materials concern the school's transfer to George Washington University and the position of GSPM president Neil Fabricant.
  - Grand Street Settlement
    - 1982-1985 (Box 53, Folder 551)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 552)
    - 1988-1991 (Box 54, Folder 553)
    - 1992-1995 (Box 54, Folder 554)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 54, Folder 555)
  - Greater Williamsburg Collaborative, 1997-1998 (Box 54, Folder 556)
  - Greenberg, Jack, 1989-1990 (Box 54, Folder 557)
    File consists of a brief exchange of correspondence with Jane Lee Eddy.
  - Groundwork Incorporated, 2003-2005 (Box 54, Folder 558)
  - Groundwork Incorporated, 2005-2006 (Box 54, Folder 559)
  - Group for the Advancement of Psychiatry, 1961-1962, 1965-1966 (Box 54, Folder 560)
  - Gutheim, Frederick (Fritz), 1964-1966 (Box 54, Folder 561)
  - Hagman, Donald G., 1971-1972 (Box 54, Folder 562)
  - Hammer, Philip
    Philip G. Hammer was on the board of directors of the Potomac Institute, and he served as a consultant to the Taconic Foundation in 1965-1966. He was particularly involved in developing the program and organization of Urban America.
    Includes a few letters from Jane Hammer.
    - 1962, 1964-1965 (Box 54, Folder 563)
    - 1966, 1969, 1984, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 564)
    - 1966 (Box 54, Folder 564 A)
  - Hampton Institute, 1961-1962, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 565)
  - Harlem Children's Zone, Inc.
    The Harlem Children's Zone began in 1997 as a project of the Rheedlen Centers for Children and Families, headed by Geoffrey Canada. The Taconic Foundation provided support for Rheedlen's Saturday Academy initiative.
    - 1996-1997 (Box 55, Folder 566)
      Oversize items have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
      - Harlem Overheard, 1997; 2014:FA407:005; 2 issues (Box 210, Item 2014:FA407:005)
        Two issues: volume 2, numbers 5 and 7 (Summer and Kwanza 1997).
    - 1998, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 567)
  - Harlem Education Program, Inc., 1966 (Box 55, Folder 568)
  - Harlem Neighborhoods Association, Inc., 1960, 1962-1964, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 569)
  - Harvard City and Regional Planning Department, 1978-1979 (Box 55, Folder 570)
    Support for survey conducted by Professor John Kain on impact of employment location and housing availability on African American workers (Bell v. Automobile Club of Michigan litigation).
  - Harvard College, 1958, 1965-1969 (Box 55, Folder 571)
    Scholarship program for underprivileged students. File includes a 1969 proposal to mobilize students in addressing urban problems.
  - Harvard Graduate School of Education: Advanced Administrative Institute, 1967-1970, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 572)
    File includes report on the Master of Arts in Teaching degree program, and proposals for a staff development center.
  - Harvard Law School: Civil Rights - Civil Liberties Research Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 55, Folder 573)
    Support for summer study of agricultural and food problems in the U. S. by law students under supervision of Derek Bok and in consultation with Ralph Nader (Nader's Raiders).
  - Harvard University: General, 1968-1970, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 574)
  - Harvard University: Efficacy Seminar (Harvard/Radcliffe), 1976-1978 (Box 55, Folder 575)
    Grant to the Afro American Cultural Center for motivational seminar to help minority students improve their academic performance.
  - Haskell, Douglas, 1965-1966, 1968, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 576)
    - Savannah streetscapes, circa 1965-1966; 2014:FA407:032; 8 still images (Item 2014:FA407:032)
  - Heart of Brooklyn Cultural Institutions, Inc., 2003-2004 March (Box 56, Folder 577)
  - Heart of Brooklyn Cultural Institutions, Inc., 2004 April - 2005 (Box 52, Folder 578)
  - Height, Dorothy, 1991-1992 (Box 56, Folder 579)
    Includes recollections of Stephen Currier's 1963 meetings with civil rights leaders.
  - HELP USA, Inc. (Fair Housing Justice Center), 2006 (Box 56, Folder 580)
  - HELP USA, Inc. (Fair Housing Justice Center), 2007 (Box 56, Folder 581)
  - Henry Street Settlement: General
    From 1969 to around 1985, the organization was also known as the Henry Street Settlement Urban Life Center.
    - 1960-1972 (Box 56, Folder 582)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 56, Folder 583)
    - 1975 (Box 56, Folder 584)
    - 1976-1978 (Box 56, Folder 585)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 56, Folder 586)
      - Map of Corlears Hook Park and East River Park Recreation Guide, 1979; 2014:FA407:006 (Item 2014:FA407:006)
    - 1981 (Box 57, Folder 587)
    - 1982-1985 (Box 57, Folder 588)
    - 1986-1990 (Box 57, Folder 589)
    - 1991-1995 (Box 57, Folder 590)
    - 1996-2000 (Box 57, Folder 591)
    - 2001 (Box 57, Folder 592)
    - 2002 (Box 57, Folder 593)
    - (Literature), 1990-1993 (Box 57, Folder 594)
  - Henry Street Settlement: Henry Street School, 1973, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 595)
    File contains 1973 report on the school and copies of student publications, 1973-1975. For grant correspondence see also the general Henry Street Settlement files.
    - Henry Street School Graduating Class, 1973 June; 2014:FA407:033; 1 still image (Item 2014:FA407:033)
  - Highbridge Community Life Center
    The Highbridge Community Life Center was located in the South Bronx.
    - 1992-1994 (Box 58, Folder 596)
    - 1995-1999 (Box 58, Folder 597)
    - 2000-2002 August (Box 58, Folder 598)
    - 2002 September - 2003 (Box 58, Folder 599)
    - 2004 (Box 58, Folder 600)
    - 2005 (Box 58, Folder 601)
  - Home Advisory and Service Council of New York, Inc., 1959-1969, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 602)
  - Horticultural Society of New York, 1977-1979 (Box 58, Folder 603)
    - Tree Corps and Community Gardening participants, 1970s; 2014:FA407:034; 5 still images (Item 2014:FA407:034)
  - Horticultural Society of New York, 1980-1985, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 604)
  - Hospitality House, 1964-1967 (Box 59, Folder 605)
    Hospitality House was a shelter and social welfare organization in Washington, D.C.
  - Housing Action Council, 1976-1978 (Box 59, Folder 606)
  - Housing and Urban Development. See United States Department of Housing and Urban Development.
  - Housing Trust Fund Project (Mary Brooks), 1986-1988 (Box 59, Folder 607)
    See also Center for Community Change: Housing Trust Fund Project.
  - Hudson Guild, 1959-1961, 1968-1972, 1985-1989 (Box 59, Folder 608)
  - Hunter College (Donna Shalala), 1982-1984, 1987-1988 (Box 59, Folder 609)
  - Patricia Skinner Huntington Associates, Inc., 1982-1983 (Box 59, Folder 610)
    Support for staffing of the Committee for Public/Private Cooperation.
  - Independent Sector
    - 1980-1982 (Box 59, Folder 611)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 59, Folder 612)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 59, Folder 613)
    - 1987-1990 (Box 60, Folder 614)
    - 1991-1995, 1999-2000 (Box 60, Folder 615)
  - Institute of Public Administration, 1961, 1964-1966 (Box 60, Folder 616)
    Support to underwrite projects of the New York City Department of City Planning and for a study of pre-school programs in New York.
  - Interface
    - 1978, 1980-1981 (Box 60, Folder 617)
    - 1982 January-October (Box 60, Folder 618)
    - 1982 November-December (Box 60, Folder 619)
    - 1983 January-May (Box 60, Folder 620)
    - 1983 June (Box 60, Folder 621)
    - 1983 July-August 15 (Box 60, Folder 622)
    - 1983 August 16-December (Box 60, Folder 623)
    - 1984 January-August (Box 61, Folder 624)
    - 1984 September - 1985 February (Box 61, Folder 625)
    - 1985 March-December (Box 61, Folder 626)
    - 1986-1989 May (Box 61, Folder 627)
    - 1989 June - 1990 (Box 61, Folder 628)
    - 1991 (Box 61, Folder 629)
    - (Literature), 1983-1985 (Box 61, Folder 630)
  - Interfaith Housing Corporation, 1970-1973 (Box 61, Folder 631)
    Boston, Mass.
  - International Center of Photography, 1996-1997 (Box 62, Folder 632)
    Support for photography program at Hunts Point, Bronx, NY.
  - Irwin-Sweeney-Miller Foundation, 1963, 1965, 1968-1969 (Box 62, Folder 633)
  - Jackson, Lincoln, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 634)
    File consists of memorandum on The Integration of the Computer in the International Curriculum.
  - Javits, Jacob K. (Senator), 1970 (Box 62, Folder 635)
    Correspondence urging Taconic Foundation support for the MESBIC (Minority Enterprise Small Business Investment Company) program in New York City.
  - Jobs for Youth
    - 1965, 1968-1974 September (Box 62, Folder 636)
    - 1974 October-December (Box 63, Folder 637)
      - Jobs for Youth poster, 1974; 2014:FA407:007 (Box 210, Item 2014:FA407:007)
    - 1975 (Box 62, Folder 638)
    - 1976 (Box 62, Folder 639)
    - 1977 (Box 62, Folder 640)
    - 1978 January-July (Box 62, Folder 641)
    - 1978 August - 1979 (Box 63, Folder 642)
    - 1980-1982 (Box 63, Folder 643)
    - 1983-1987 (Box 63, Envelope 644)
    - 1988-1991 (Box 63, Folder 645)
    - (Literature), 1973-1975 (Box 63, Folder 646)
    - (Literature), 1980-1984, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 647)
  - Jobs for Youth - Boston, 1983-1985 (Box 63, Folder 648)
  - James Weldon Johnson Community Center, 1961-1970 (Box 63, Folder 649)
  - Johnson, Robert M., 1990-1994 (Box 63, Folder 650)
    Robert Matthews Johnson evaluated the Gautreaux program for Business and Professional People for the Public Interest. For the Taconic Foundation's support related to the Gautreaux decision, see the files for Business and Professional People for the Public Interest.
  - Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies
    The Joint Center of Political Studies was originally affiliated with Howard University. In March 1990 it changed its name to Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies.
    In 1984, the Taconic Foundation contributed $7,500 toward the costs of the Fourth National Policy Institute for black elected and appointed officials, of which the Joint Center was a sponsor.
    - 1973-1975 (Box 63, Folder 651)
    - 1976 (Box 63, Folder 652)
    - 1977, 1980-1983 (Box 64, Folder 653)
    - 1984 (Box 64, Folder 654)
    - 1985 (Box 64, Folder 655)
    - 1986 (Box 64, Folder 656)
    - 1987 (Box 64, Folder 657)
    - 1988 (Box 64, Folder 658)
    - 1989 (Box 64, Folder 659)
    - 1990 (Box 64, Folder 660)
    - 1991-1993 (Box 65, Folder 661)
    - 1994 (Box 65, Folder 662)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 663)
    - (Literature and Reports), 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 664)
      Library materials have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
      - The Congressional Black Caucus in the 103rd Congress, by David A. Bositis, 1994; 2014:FA407:055; 1 bound volume (Item 2014:FA407:055)
    - (Literature and Reports), 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 665)
      Includes Joint Center publications by David Bositis on Blacks and the 1996 Democratic National Convention; Blacks and the 1996 Republican National Convention; and Redistricting and Representation.
  - Klasen, James
    Klasen served as a consultant for the Taconic Foundation in October-December 1983, to help in the development of a comprehensive youth employment policy in Dutchess County, NY. The file includes his weekly reports.
    - 1983-1984 February (Box 65, Folder 666)
    - 1984 March - 1985 (Box 65, Folder 667)
  - Knoxville College, 1961-1964, 1966, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 668)
  - Kohler, Judge Mary Conway (Youth and Work Project), 1962-1963 (Box 65, Folder 669)
    File concerns publication and dissemination of reports on "Youth and Work in New York City" and "Youth in the World of Work," based on a national survey on youth employment conducted by the Taconic Foundation. Mary Kohler was a consultant and principal investigator for the project.
  - Kohler, Judge Mary Conway (Youth and Work Project), 1962-1963 (Box 65, Folder 669 A)
    Restricted material - Confidential.
  - Kuttner, Robert L. (Consultant), 1978-1981, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 670)
    Project file. Kuttner was hired as a consultant to write a general piece evaluating the success of Neighborhood Housing Services.
  - Kuttner, Robert L. (Consultant), 1978-1981, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 670 A)
  - Landrum, Roger, 1971-1972, 1988-1989 (Box 66, Folder 671)
    See also The Teachers Incorporated, for additional materials pertaining to Landrum.
    Correspondence on teacher training; Youth Service America newsletters.
  - Lawson, Ronald (City University of New York, Queens College), 1979-1986 (Box 66, Folder 672)
    Support for study of tenant activism and housing abandonment in New York City.
  - Law Students Civil Rights Research Council
    - 1963-1965 August (Box 66, Folder 673)
    - 1965 September - 1966 (Box 66, Folder 674)
    - 1967-1971 (Box 66, Folder 675)
    - 1972-1977 (Box 66, Folder 676)
  - Lawyers Alliance for New York
    Up until 1992, the Lawyers Alliance for New York was known as the Council of New York Law Associates.
    For earlier materials see files for Council of New York Law Associates.
    - 1992 (Box 66, Folder 677)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 66, Folder 678)
    - 1995 (Box 67, Folder 679)
    - 1996-2001 (Box 67, Folder 680)
    - 2002-2005 (Box 67, Folder 681)
    - 2006-2007 (Box 67, Folder 682)
    - (Literature), 1996-1999 (Box 67, Folder 683)
  - Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights under Law: General
    - 1965, 1970-1972 (Box 67, Folder 684)
    - 1973 (Box 67, Folder 685)
    - 1974-1976 (Box 68, Folder 686)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 68, Folder 687)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 68, Folder 688)
    - 1982-1987 (Box 68, Folder 689)
    - 1988-1991 (Box 68, Folder 690)
    - 1992-1994 (Box 68, Folder 691)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 68, Folder 692)
    - 1997 (Box 68, Folder 693)
    - 1998-2003 (Box 68, Folder 694)
    - (Literature), circa 1992, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 695)
  - Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights under Law: New York Committee, Community School System Project
    - 1969-1970 (Box 69, Folder 696)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 69, Folder 697)
  - Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights under Law: School Desegregation Study Project, 1970-1971 (Box 69, Folder 698)
  - Lawyers Constitutional Defense Committee
    The Lawyers Constitutional Defense Committee (LCDC) was absorbed by the American Civil Liberties Union's Roger Baldwin Foundation in 1968.
    - 1964-1967 (Box 69, Folder 699)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 69, Folder 700)
  - Lawyers Military Defense Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 69, Folder 701)
    The Lawyers Military Defense Committee became affiliated with the American Civil Liberties Union in 1971.
  - Leadership Conference Education Fund
    - 1985-1986 (Box 69, Folder 702)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 69, Folder 703)
    - 1989-1991 (Box 70, Folder 704)
  - Leadership Council for Metropolitan Open Communities, 1992-1995 (Box 70, Folder 705)
  - League for Industrial Democracy, 1963-1966 (Box 70, Folder 706)
    Apprenticeship training program for minority youth.
  - League for Industrial Democracy, 1967-1974, 1978 (Box 70, Folder 707)
  - League of Women Voters: Mike McManus, 1979, 1982 (Box 70, Folder 708)
    Michael J. McManus wrote a series of articles in connection with the League of Women Voters' "Tri-State Town Meeting" project.
  - League of Women Voters Education Fund: General
    - 1974-1977 (Box 70, Folder 709)
    - 1980-1982 (Box 70, Folder 710)
    - 1983-1985 (Box 70, Folder 711)
    - 1986 (Box 70, Folder 712)
    - 1987-1988 October (Box 70, Folder 713)
    - 1988 November - 1989 (Box 71, Folder 714)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 71, Folder 715)
  - League of Women Voters Education Fund: Exclusionary Zoning Program
    - 1967-1972 (Box 71, Folder 716)
    - 1973-1974, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 717)
  - League of Women Voters Education Fund: Literature
    - 1969-1977 (Box 71, Folder 718)
      File contains newsletters, brochures, and covering correspondence. Includes program brochure for National Conference on Open Suburbs (at the Johnson Foundation, Wingspread), March 27-28, 1973.
    - 1972 (Box 71, Folder 719)
      File Plan
      Proposal to the Taconic Foundation to provide educational services to community leaders who seek to work effectively on exclusionary zongin and low-income housing in the suburbs, with attachments, February 1972.
    - 1977 (Box 71, Folder 720)
      File contains attachments from the League's final narrative and financial report on the National Revenue Sharing Monitoring Project.
    - 1983-1986 (Box 71, Folder 721)
      File includes published reports on the League's Voting Rights Act Monitoring and Litigation Project.
  - Lebby, Marsha J., 1983 (Box 71, Folder 722)
    Lebby was hired as a consultant to prepare the text for the Taconic Foundation's twenty-five-year report.
  - Lebby, Marsha J., 1983 (Box 71, Folder 722 A)
  - Legal Aid Society
    - 1958-1964, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 723)
    - 1969-1974, 1979-1987 (Box 72, Folder 724)
    - (Literature), 1967-1971 (Box 72, Folder 725)
      Includes Annual Reports for 1967 and 1968 and Community Law Offices reference guides.
    - (Literature), 1971 (Box 72, Folder 726)
      File contains Community Law Offices' Second Annual Report, July 1, 1969 through December 31, 1970.
  - Legal Outreach, Inc., 1999-2006 (Box 72, Folder 727)
    Support for College Bound program.
  - Lehman College: Institute for Literacy Studies, 1995-1996 November (Box 72, Folder 728)
  - Lehman College: Institute for Literacy Studies, 1996 December -1997 (Box 72, Folder 729)
  - Levin, Arthur, 1969-1970, 1982, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 730)
    File contains correspondence with Jane Lee Eddy.
  - Adele R. Levy Park Committee, 1963-1965 (Box 72, Folder 731)
  - Literacy Assistance Center, Inc.
    Support for Mayor's Literacy Project, a training program proposed by the Office of the Mayor of New York.